She has the code. He is the key.
Safe is a action, crime, thriller film directed by Boaz Yakin.
After a former elite agent rescues a 12-year-old Chinese girl who's been abducted, they find themselves in the middle of a
standoff between Triads, the Russian Mafia and high-level corrupt New York City politicians and police.
Luke Wright, played by Jason Statham.
Mayor Tremello, played by Chris Sarandon.
Han Jiao, played by James Hong.
Mei, played by Catherine Chan.
Captain Wolf, played by Robert John Burke.
Alex Rosen, played by Anson Mount.
Safe is a 2012 American action thriller film written and directed by Boaz Yakin, produced by Lawrence Bender, Dana
Brunetti, and Joseph Zolfo, and starring Jason Statham, Chris Sarandon, Robert John Burke, and James Hong.
In the film, Luke Wright, an ex-cop and former cage fighter, winds up protecting a gifted child
being chased by the Russian mafia, Chinese triads, and corrupt NYPD officers.
Safe was released by Lionsgate Films on April 27, 2012;
it received mixed reviews from critics.
The film grossed $40.6 million worldwide against a budget of $30 million.
The film explores themes of new york city, triad, corrupt politician.
The tone is intense.